[{"answer": "First of all, I would have started two years ago supplying weapons to the Syrian opposition and I think that Bashar Assad would have been gone but that's over.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "Let me ask you a question, if you had been president and through this crisis right now, under what circumstances would you have gone to Congress to seek permission effectively the military action in Syria?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "... that's a moral equivalency which is not true.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "How did it come to that?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Not surprised.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard about this?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "I think we give him a lot more respect than he deserves.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Does he respect America anymore than America respects him and Russia?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Do you remember that?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "I think it's premature.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Are we being unfair?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "The bigger picture is Iran is the key.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "But what is the bigger picture particularly for America and the region?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, it has been one of pillars of American foreign policy in modern times are both president of Democratic and Republican presidents that we don't stick our nose in other people's business at least in theory, except when it resents a danger to American national security or it goes over a certain line, I'm not talking about a red line now, of conscience.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What is it the business of America?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "I think for a lot of people it does.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "ORGAN: Did Syria crossed that line, the one you're talking about?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Is he a necessary evil in this -- John Kerry says not a game and it's not for those who are being bombed and losing their lives, but in a sense we're in the middle of a very sophisticated political chest game here, is Putin in the end a necessary evil to get to where perhaps America would prefer to be?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "No, it's the first time I've actually heard that analysis.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Bill Kristol, so apparently Vladimir Putin blinked, do you go along with that?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, the last time I looked Bill it was Barack Obama that threatened military action and then Putin said, \"OK, we'll cooperate and so ...", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "So Putin is the one who backed down here is that right?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I'll agree that if Syria has no chemical weapons that that's a great thing, but let's not for one second think that Vladimir Putin's interest are anything but Vladimir Putin increasing his own power, period.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Kristen, you're in the middle here or far away?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Well, certainly the Wall Street Journal and the New York Post just the big two.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Which one would you say -- which one would you say is Bill?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "I mean Kristen this is not exactly a win-win for America or the President, is it?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know I think this diplomatic process can go on and off a long time.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Bill Kristol at what point does Barack Obama have to do a military strike to maintain credibility here?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "I'd like to clear a message which I think until his speech was lacking.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "If you were advising President Obama right now, what would you be advising him to do?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, if Bill turns out to be too pessimistic and I turn out to be correctly optimistic, those chemical weapons get taken away from Assad, the opposition in Syria that John McCain and Lindsey Graham have identified are not jihadists that our civic and political and secular small democrats need to be strengthened and then maybe in the long run Bill will look back and come to agree with me sometimes that can be possible.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "I think that is a given but that doesn't seem to be enough to drive the American public to want to take military action, how does Barack Obama deal with that eventuality if the Russian game plan stalls?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "You're implying that somehow blind people are less than you are because you can see.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "What possible sense can there be in people who literally cannot see at all wielding a firearm at anyone that possibly comes into their home?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Wait a minute.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "It's 4:00 a.m. how many times that your neighbor comes over?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "The blind people that I've talked to today, that have e-mailed and called and send tweets to me have said overwhelmingly especially those that are single and live alone that they think that they should have the right, keyword in their home, to be able to protect themselves and I ask you again the same question is the question I asked you earlier.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Ben, do you think the blind people agree with you that they should have the right to have guns?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I am not blind and nor are you.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "And wait for 15, 20 minutes?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "I think any person ...", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "So you would like everyone who's totally blind in America, just to clarify to have the right to bear arms, which means at the moment and we've discussed this before, they could have the right to have say an AR15?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "... that is blind, that is willing to go through and make sure what is correct for them.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I don't think the majority of blind people are somehow dumb and are going to think that's the appropriate weapon for them.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Will you be happy for blind people in America to be armed with one of those -- for anyone that perhaps not so in my door in the middle of the night?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I have always been a country girl.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "So what's it like to be a country girl?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "You -- I mean you're the cat with nine lives in many ways aren't you?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "No paparazzi.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "No paparazzi?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "I kind of think of like who's the worst serial killer I could have dated.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "You then hook up with the guy who turns out to be the most scandalized sportsman in American history, something easy brute is it?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Are you kidding me?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "It's been a long time.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What is the secret?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "But what is the secret to looking at least a decade younger than me?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "It's good MTV TV brought in (ph).", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Should we be offended by this?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I can't answer that.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Why would you all getting proverbial in it (ph) as in a twist?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I will tell you that I came out with my first record when I was 28.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "What do you feel about all the controversy over it all?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "We're good, clean, family entertainment around here.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Anything you want to tell me?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "You know, it's funny.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Can you calm my fury about what he did?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "You ever talked to him?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Have you?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "And we'll talk about it some PG tips laid out (ph).", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Anyone you want to share with the group?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Many.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I got rid of the -- yeah, I (inaudible) marry but I still have the sketches.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Does that something you feel sorry?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "You know it's funny, I've read a couple of times that Jennifer Anniston have been -- the two of us have been dumped more than any two people but, its' not true.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Are you always the heartless dumpy in these, do you always the one that breaks it out?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Are you high maintenance?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Funny.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "What bumps does he going to take?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I started out before VH1 to -- obviously people do know how old I am.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "What's the big ambition for you?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "They don't.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "I saw you found (ph) your McDonalds jingle on YouTube, yet?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "10 to 40 ...", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Yes, it went national and yes, got my car and went to LA took my tapes around and got a Johnny Mathis session.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "For 45 minutes work?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Maybe just career-wise probably my first Grammys.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "What's the one you choose?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Oh, God, wait.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "I can say it to your eye, you can have the best sex you've ever had in your life again or that Grammy moment which one would you take?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "I might take the Grammy.", "docId": "130912pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "You'd take the Grammy there wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 585}]